trutechtools.com 2009-04-29

# Privacy Notice : TruTech Tools, Tools for "Tru" Technicians

**Privacy**

We realize that making purchases at TruTech Tools.com, or any other website, requires trust on your part. We value your trust, and pledge to you, our customer, that we will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us, and that your personal information will only be used as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

 **The Information You Provide  
** The security of your personal information is very important to us. We collect personal information that you choose to voluntarily provide. This information includes your email address make a purchase. We may also ask for personal information when you contact a Customer Service Representative. This allows us to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity.

When you make a purchase using a credit card, we collect your name, billing address, card type, first and last four card numbers and expiration date. We only use third party secure sites on a secure SSL in order to complete your transaction. We do collect information that allows us to ship your order. This includes the name, address and phone number of the intended recipient(s). Your password for our site is your password, therefore we cannot retrieve this information if you loose it, nor can we place orders for you under your account. 

From time to time, TruTech Tools may conduct surveys and contests via our website, email or other media. If you choose to participate, we may request your name, email address, mailing address and other personal information.

 **Cookies  
** TruTech Tools.com does not use permanent cookies. However, online shopping does require per-session cookies. As soon as you close your browser, these temporary cookies are deleted. You can browse TruTech Tools.com with cookies disabled, but you will be unable to purchase items.

TruTech Tools does not allow third party cookies. If you come to TruTech Tools.com through one of our affiliate websites, they may place a permanent cookie on your computer. This cookie is only used to track click-through rates from our affiliates.

 **Additional Computer Information  
** We collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during, a visit to TruTech Tools.com. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, operation system, browser type and the address of a referring website. We do not sell or rent this information, the information we collect is only used to enhance our customers' shopping experience, improve our internal searches and to develop aggregate information about our customer base and usage patterns.

 **How We Use Your Personal Information  
** Information we collect on TruTech Tools.com may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways: 

  *  Confirming your orders
  *  Delivering the merchandise that you purchase online 
  *  Responding to your customer-service inquires or requests 
  *  Communicating special offers and featured items to you (if you choose to receive such notices) 
  *  Finding and stocking the products you want 
  *  Customizing your shopping experience 

TruTech Tools may also use the information collected to notify visitors of changes to the site and for any other legitimate and lawful business purpose. TruTech Tools may choose to share information with third parties, such as suppliers, financial institutions, and third party service providers, and with any successor to TruTech Tools's interest. TruTech Tools may disclose information about any site visitor when required by law.

Aside from the purposes described above, we will never share your personal information with any third parties unless we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when required by law. We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

 **The Communications You Receive From Us  
** If you choose to receive periodic communications from us, we may, from time to time, send you email messages with new items, featured merchandise and special offers. You can choose to stop receiving these emails at any time. Simply reply to the email with the word, "Unsubscribe" in the subject line.

The only email messages you will receive from TruTech Tools when you elect not to receive informational emails, will be to confirm any purchases made, let you know your order has shipped, response to Customer Service inquiries and answer any other questions you may have about our site. We may also need to send operational emails to inform you of any changes to our site that might affect your personal information or to announce product recalls.
